https://www.frankwrightmundy.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyHomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyWhy do we collect information?Frank Wright Mundy is committed to protecting your privacy. The information collected about you is so that we can process orders effectively, provide you with a better shopping experience and ensuring that you can shop online safely and securely.What information do we collect?When you order online, we need to know your name, address, e-mail address and delivery address, your credit or debit card details are handled by secure and verified payment portals, WorldPay or Paypal, we do not process any credit or debit card details.We may also ask for your telephone number this is to enable us to contact you if there is a problem with your order. We do not collect sensitive personal data.We do not keep a copy of your credit/debit card details on any of our systems once your payment has been approved – this is why you will always be asked to add it at each point of sale.How does Frank Wright Mundy use this information?We automatically collect information through our website. Like many websites we use "cookies" which allows us to keep your shopping basket updated whilst you shop and if you return to our website your items will have remained in your shopping cart. As noted below if you do not accept the use of cookies at a browser level you won’t be able to use the website to purchase goods as intended – but you can still telephone 01745 827451 and do so. We also analyse traffic to our website such as the number of visitors and pages visited; however this cannot be linked to personal information.Specifically we may use this data:For our own internal recordsTo improve products and services we provideTo contact you in response to a specific enquiryOnly if requested, to send you promotional emails about products, services, special offers and salesTo contact you via email, telephone or mail for market research purposes.What is a Cookie?A Cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive. It enables our website to identify your computer as you view different pages on our website.Cookies allow websites and applications to store your preferences in order to present content, options or functions that are specific to you. They also enable us to see information like how many people use the website and what pages they tend to visit.How we use Cookies?Analyse our web traffic using an analytics package. Aggregated usage data helps us improve the website structure, design, content and functions.Identify whether you are signed in to our website. A Cookie allows us to check whether you are signed in to the site.Store information about your preferences.To recognise when you return to our website, so you do not have to complete all your delivery and billing address details each time.Cookies DO NOT provide us with access to your computer or any information about you, other than that which you choose to share with us.How can I control Cookies?When you first access our website or if you clear your cookies you will be asked to confirm your cookie settings. Here you will also be able to see a full list of the cookies we use and turn on or off any cookies that you would prefer not to have.If you change your mind you can alter this at any time on our Cookie Declaration page.You can also use your web browser’s cookie settings to determine how websites use cookies.  If you do not want websites to store cookies on your computer or device you should set your web browser to refuse cookies, though please note that some cookies allow for website functions to work, so if you are experiencing any issues first try re-enabling cookies.How does Frank Wright Mundy protect customer information?Our website is secured and encrypted using strong TLS. This means that all information you input is encrypted before it is sent to us. We regularly review the security standards and ensure that we adapt to new risks as they develop. Furthermore, as required by the UK Data Protection Acts of 1984 and 1998, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information that you provide, to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you.Do we share your information?In order to process certain product orders we share delivery information with our agents for their due processing and in these cases these third parties have access to information which may only be used for that purpose and must be treated in accordance with this privacy statement and the Data Protection Acts described above.We do not sell your personal data or information to any third party organisations.Do we disclose your information?We may disclose your information in special cases when we have reason to believe that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with the law, apply or enforce our terms and conditions, or to protect our rights.What is the e-mail policy of Frank Wright MundyOnce you have registered an account, placed an order or left feedback with www.frankwrightmundy.co.uk on the phone or via the website you may receive an e-mail confirming your order or to thank you for doing so as a way of confirming receipt of the information you have provided.If you are interested in special offers, sales or information that may be of interest, you must register to our mailing list, which you can do on the homepage towards the bottom of the screen.Should you later choose that you would prefer not to receive these e-mails, or believe you have mistakenly been added to the mailing list please use the unsubscribe option or contact us at sales@frankwrightmundy.co.ukIn some cases we will reach out to you in order to query an issue with your order or account. In these cases we are contacting you out of necessity and try to do so at a minimum.Emails received from Frank Wright MundyEmail messages and any associated files are confidential, intended solely for the use of the individual or entity to whom they are addressed and contain the views of the author. If you have received a FWM email in error, please reply immediately and delete it from your computer. FWM shall not be bound by anything stated in an email and shall not be liable for any losses as a result of virus transmission, although endeavours are made to protect against this. E-mails are susceptible to alteration.
